Guide to the Records of the History Department of the Faculty of Arts and Science 1926-1978 (Bulk 1960-1970) RG 21.3 RG 21.3
New York University Archives
Records of the History Department of the Faculty of Arts and Science
Bulk, 1960-1970
1926-1978
RG 21.3
New York University Archives
14.0 linear feet (14 boxes)
This collection contains administrative records of the History Department. Materials include staff files, budget information, and correspondence.
New York University. Dept. of History.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged by subject.
The files are grouped into 1 series:
Administrative Records
Related Material at the New York University Archives
There are two interviews regarding the history department with professors Carl Prince and David Hicks in the Records of the NYU Public History Program
Box 15, folders 6 and 7.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains administrative records of the History Department. Materials include staff files, budget information, and correspondence.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Department of History is located within the Faculty of Arts and Science at NYU. History has been taught at NYU since the University's founding in 1831, but it was not until 1893 that NYU formed academic departments, including one in history. Courses are offered to undergraduates and graduates.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Provenance
This collection was transferred to the University Archives from the History Department.
New York University. Faculty of Arts and Science.; New York University.; Administrative records.; Correspondence.; Memorandums.; Reports.; Universities and colleges |x Departments.; Universities and colleges |x Faculty.
- Series I: Administrative Records
  - Approved Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 3 1142 042263197
  - All-University Department of History - Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226319 7
  - Summer Session, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Commerce and Education - Acquisitions From, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Salary Increase Data, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Department Meeting, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Department Vote on Promotions, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Travel Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Travel Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - All-University Department of History - Official Budget, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Working Papers and SS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - History Budget, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget Data - Clerical, 1950-1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Budget - History Department, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Budget - History Department, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - History Department Budget, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Budget - History Department, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget - History Department, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Budget - History Department, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Budget - History Department, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget - History Department, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Budget - History Department, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Budget - History Department, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Policy Re: Clerical Personnel, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Barbash, Miss Sonia, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Unemployment Claims, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Secretarial - Employment Procedures, Overtime, Salaries, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Alston, Miriam (Office Temporary), undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Archimovich, Tatiana, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Baronovska, Isabella, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bates, Mildred (Office Temporary), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Butler, Jane S., undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Carley, Mary, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Caruso, Connie, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sara Chesner - Secretary, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ciangiola, Jeanette, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Derringh, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Draponette, Ree (Office Temporary), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dreiblatt, Arline (Office Temporary), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Mrs. Lillian Duane, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fields, Liza, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Galizia, Regina, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Givone, Elide (Office Temporary), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Hayes, Caroline, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Kaminsky, Rosalie, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Karosik, Anita, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Katz, Esther (Graduate History Student Who Helped with Registration), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Lifton, Ruth, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Mrs. Josephine McNally, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Patricia McQuilldy (Part-time), undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Macauley, Sheila, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Mack, Yvonne, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Margulies, Diane, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Meiselbar, Grace, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Millen, Angela, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Helene Murawsky (Temporary), undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Judith Nichols, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - O'Neill, Janitzia (Office Temporary), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Schafler, Pamela, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Rita Selner - Secretary, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Scharoff, Ethel - Stern, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Siegel, Judith, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Stickman, Marian, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Tondetter, Evelyn, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Varon, Mrs. Susan (Temporary), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Williams, Mehta, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Wilson, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Wolf, Rochelle, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Wool, Harvey, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Zamosky, Phyllis, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Zimmer, Mildred C., undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Budget Data, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Budget, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Department Budget, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Summer, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Summer, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Deans, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Budger, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Budget (Official and Letters), 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Personnel and Tenure Lists, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Budget Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Budget: History and American Civ., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - History Department Spec. Fund 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Gallatin Funds and Papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Budget Planning, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226320 5
  - Taylor Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - James Stokes Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Josiah Macy, Jr. Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget Planning, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Department Schedule, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - WSC, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - University College, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Personnel - Clerical, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Income Estimate (Washington Square), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Civilization Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Summer Session, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Summer Session, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Summer Session, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session Budget, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Summer Session, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Summer Session Plans, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Summer, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Budget Plans, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Budget Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - GAF Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Travel Grants - Summer, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - WSC Budget, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - UC, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - WSC Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - GAS Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - GAS Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Budget - UC, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Washington Square College Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Budget Information, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Budget GSAS, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - GAS Budget, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Assignment Chart, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Assignment Chart, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - GAS Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Budget WSC, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Budget - Univ. Coll., 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Duty Allocation, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Winder Conference, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Assignment Chart, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Budget WSC, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Macy Fnd. Check, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - GAS, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - GAS Special Funds, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Budget Working Papers and Info, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Budget - Univ. Coll., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Budget Conference - Deans, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - GAS Bulletin Copy - Summer Session, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Summer Sessions, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Entertainment Fund, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Visiting Professors Stipend, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - GAS Budgets, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Official Budget Letters, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Budget - Univ. Coll., 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Summer Session, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Travel Reimbursement, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Summer Session, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Summer Session Budget and Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Budget Worksheets - Univ. Coll., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Salary Statistics, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Policy Meeting, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Policy Committee, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Courses, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Petty Cash, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Bulletin Copy, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226321 3
  - Faculty Bulletin - Publication List, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Colloquium Rules, 0000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter (history), 0000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni meetings/graduate history, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Club, Grad History, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gifts to Dept Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Doctoral List, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Draft, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - War, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Meeting of Faculty and Students to Discuss the War, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fields for Phd, content of discussion, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Fund Drive, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Rules on Grades, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NYU Staff Newspaper, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Summer Institutes, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Strike Info, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - History Dept and Strikers, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Washington Square Strike, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Grades - GSAS, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Ph.D exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Honors, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gerstenblith, Gary, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Cohen, James A., undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Grad, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fellowships - Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - U57.0081 - Lecture Schedule, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - History Dept, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - History Dept, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Grad History Society, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - The Historian, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Honors, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Letters to Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Letters for Students, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Photos, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 51LS - Back, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 51RL - Back, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 51 Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 51- Final Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - 61LS, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - 61RL, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 61 Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - 38 - Readings, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - 73 Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - 73RL - Back, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 73RL - Current, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - 73LS, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 83 LS Back, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - 83 RL Back, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - 83 Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - 83 Final Exams, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - NW Courses, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - W and M course, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Administration Dept of History - 19 Univ. Pl, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Advisory Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Advisory Committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - WSC Advisory Committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Advisory Committee Meetings GSAS, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Advisory Committee Meetings, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Advisory Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Advisory Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Arts and Science Heads (Council), undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Meeting re: possible interdisciplinary seminar (Zartman), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - All University Departments, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Meetins of Full Profs of History Dept Personnel, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Dept Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Dept Meetings, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Meetings of Heads, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Meetings Washington Square Heads, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - All Heads and Program Chairmen Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Heads and Directors Meetings (Budgetary, etc), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - All Heads Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - All University Heads Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Heads Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Heads Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226324 4
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - All University Dept. Heads Meeting and Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Studies Association, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - President's Council on Grad. Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - GSAS Minutes, Chairman, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - GSAS, WSC Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GSAS, WSC Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - GSAS Faculty Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Girard, Chairman and Director of Grad Studies, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Primary Appointments - GAS, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Committees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Committee Dept, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Goals Committee, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Grievance Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Library Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Selection Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Social Science Chairman Committee, School of Ed, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Social Studies, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - UH Faculty Meeting, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Educational Policy Committee, University College, 1959-1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Committee (Hindle), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Advisory Committee (Caruso, Chairman), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Grants - NEDA etc, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Cash meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Dept Meeting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Dept Meeting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Dept Meeting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Dept Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gershoy Memorial Service, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Library Committee, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Personnel Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Personnel Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Promotional Campaign, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Retirement, Early, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Rosenthal, Prof. Joel, 0000 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Sabbatical Leaves, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Sabbatical Leaves, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Sabbatical Leaves, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Social Science Dept Cooperation, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Student Alumni Meeting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Student Conferences, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Teaching Schedules - Dept, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Travel Funds (Meetings), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Undergraduate Program, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - University Task Force, rept., undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Winder, Dean Bayly, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Winder Meetings, Heads and Chairmen, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Advisory Committee, Creation of and rules governing, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Advisory Committee Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Dept Meeting, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Dept Meeting General, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Dept Meeting Grad, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Dept Meeting Grad, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Dept Meeting General, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Dept Meeting, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Dept Meeting General, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Dept Meetings, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226328 8
  - Dept Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dept Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dept Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dept Meetings, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dept Meetings, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dept Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dept Meetings, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Dept Meetings, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dept Meetings, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Grad Student Attitudes/Reactions, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Student Advisory, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Student Faculty Committee on Graduate Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Department Evaluation, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Student Participation, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Tenure Questions, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tenure Correspodence, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tenure and Promotions, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Tenure Practices, other departments, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - University College Tenure Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Relations/Grad, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - History Department Descriptions, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Africa Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Negro History, books on, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Negro History, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - African Studies, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Black Students, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Oral History Projects, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Post of Director of Graduate Studies Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Elton Golden, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: General, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Current Affairs on Campus, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Recent Communications, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines:Dean, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Department, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Rules of Conduct, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines:Distribution, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Recent Statements, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Recently Distributed Materials, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: University Finances, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Purposes, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: President Hester, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: University Senate, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Committee on University Purposes and Guidelines: Drafts, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Calendar, 1957-1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Education/Grants, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Knedler, substitute, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Other History Dept (practice), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Flat Fee Commission, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Language Requirement, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Language Requirement, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Committee Reports, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Cartter Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Symposia on Teaching, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Baker, George R.F, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226331 2